This is part of your heart on a chip and
it could one day save your life.
Scientists made them by scanning the
arteries of real patients with varying
degrees of disease and creating a 3D
image that they then 3D printed onto a
piece of glass and then used it to make
a 3D replica of the real thing on a
chip. And then they send fluid through
the models to track how blood flows. And
right there in white is a blood clot
forming. And they found that blood clots
not just because of how narrow your
artery is, but also how its unique shape
makes the blood flow. So, they're hoping
to use these chips to make
patientspecific treatments and develop
new drugs.